I built
Tomodachi Life
in Minecraft!
When clicking on these types of videos
you’d probably expect...
ULTIMATE
HARDCORE
MILLIONS OF BLOCKS
...resource gathering
AND
DEATH
well...
i did none of that.
i’m the biggest looser when it comes to
this game’s survival mode
i always end up loosing my progress and friends :c
okay we’re good to go!
uh...
NO
i’m dying!
[beep]
NO
no
[beep]
I’m the odd type of person that finds
Minecraft’s fun in creative mode!
and for years
i’ve carried on the back of my head the idea to
build my own Tomodachi Life Island. . .
So!
now that I'm back in my creative spirit,
not bed rotting away my life,
and found some cool tools to play with,
it’s the perfect recipe for what you’re about to see!
Hope you like it!
I decided to lay out the island and its buildings first,
and as I built I started getting more ideas of
how to adapt tomodachi life to minecraft,,
however there was a teeny issue . . .
some things are like BIG
sorry about my voice
i was sick that day :c
and like actually like...
like ACTUAL BUILDINGS
“oh yeah! i can recreate this in minecraft”
...and some things are more like
little icons
like Mii Homes...
they’re like little tiny small
...things
compared to the main building
I continued building and i had fun,
i even found out some new stuff along the way
* shock *
<---- notices stone behind
that’s what THESE are...
stairs!
for the miis to go down!
how did i never notice that...
And with that, I had finished the foundation,
I decided to add the texturing and detailing on my own,
and I think it came out pretty neat c:
I got to try some new things, and it really felt
like I was painting a soon to be masterpiece. . .
Once that was done, I decided to stream again,
and i had some surprises
this is my apartment building...
there’s much easier ways to access, but-
*gasp*
oh! here’s one of the surprises...
(the dog i lost in my survival world)
also known as “borf”
credit to: @JokaRen_
Dinky!
it’s over here...
what??
Tomodachi Life?
in Minecraft?
we have the tomodachi life music!
isn’t that cool?
will be included in the world download :>
I was experimenting with uhh...
with armour stands!
uh so... over here i have the pau mii
and ...mii gunner
wow!
it would be cool if i had a roller coaster type thing...
that got you from here to down there
it’d be a cool and smart idea to have all the island
connected
whenever you spawn in you’ll be able to explore
and everything will be pretty accesible
i have an elevator up, but like...
Building the Observation Tower
i guess the way to get down would be here
tap the button here,
...i think that’s better for everyone
*gasp*
a cloud!
it’s an AIRPLANE!
omigosh... i’ve never seen that before!
(getting distracted)
who often gets mistaken for...
Nikki Swapdoodle
*gasp*
me!
that’s-
that’s it
this is the tower!
hooray!
Building the Interior Shop
woah! there’s orange wool...
hm...
perfect!
a dead bush...
*gasp*
that’s so cool!
okay, yeah
yeah, i feel like that’s the best of both worlds
Building the Town Hall
yeah, i really don’t like that...
okay, yea, that’ll do it
finished!!
haha
no
i need the back...
yeah, i really do not like that...
the town hall doesn’t have an inside
...i guess the mii apartments
...do have an inside
...i don’t know how i’m gonna do that
maybe 2... or 3,, (variants of) the default interiors
Building Mii Apartments
and then i’ll copy that so there’s
(counting) 1,2,3,4,5,6,7,8....
okay... yea, that doesn’t look too bad
And so began the final steps:
building all the stores,
the mii apartments and homes,
all of the recreational areas,
the mii news tower,
the amusement park,
the cafe, the photo area, and more,,
at this point i realized that this was something much
bigger than what i was expecting,,
and i decided to do some building on my own.
Building the Concert Hall
when i made my first stream i had the idea
to make this like a lobby, here
and then, you go down here...
you’ll be able to see that there’s this whole area
yeah! the first time i used the oak planks i was like
*gasp*
that kind of looks like Mr. Tomo...
♪ your best foot forward ♪
here’s the muscial cover you’ve
all been waiting for
♪ on Jupiter or Mars ♪
♪ sha la la la space dreamin’ ♪
♪ this galaxy’s too small ♪
Building the Cafe
yeah! i like the
how they’re always talking
although they do repeat themselves
and they even acknowledge it
well to be fair Tomodachi Life really likes meta jokes
where they’re like
☝
oh!
wow!
*achoo*
sorry
let’s move on to the next... thing
aaa that looks cool,,, i like that!
yeah! i’m doing the pawn shop!
Building the Pawn Shop
we’re just making the pawn shop, the hat shop,
and the food mart
we’re almost done! we’re in the homestretch
so much of my personality and everything about me
relies so much in sleepiness...
you know how youtubers sometimes name their audience?
what if i named you guys, my viewers...
sleepyheads
whenever i start a video i go like
“ good morning sleepyheads!”
what?
whoops
yeah, i think that’ll just about do it for the pawn shop...
i don’t think i can do much more
i’’ always find a way to sneek in a trans flag!
yeah i really like that!
Building the Food Mart
i’m proud of myself! ^^
so close! so close!
i love that!!
i love that!
so much,,
i’m cooking
cooking!
there we go!
that’s so cool,, i love that,,
i think this is the first time i’ve been so excited for
a minecraft build
we have Mr. Tomo!
it even kind of looks like a face...
that’s Mr. Tomo!
hi Mr. Tomo!
i think we’re fine... i think-
i think-
we’re done
and with that
my life-long dream of building
Tomodachi Life in Minecraft was complete!
I’ll have a schematic and a world-download in
the description so you can explore it or build it yourself!
hope you enjoyed!
i know that my channel is mainly centered
around my animations
but i thought i could try something different
If you’re interested in more of my minecraft stuff,
please subscribe to my second channel “Pau archives”!
and also please subscribe to this channel as well,
it would help a lot
oki!
thanks for watching!
good nightey!